Guide to the Doris Duke Foundation records, 1934-2009 (bulk 1948-1982)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1934-2009
  - The Children’s Village: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clipping, 1955–1970 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Citizen’s Committee on Children of New York City: Donations, Closed Files, 1952–1966 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Citizens for the All-Day Neighborhood Schools: Donations, Closed Files. Includes photograph, 1955–1960 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - City Federation Hotel Center – Center for Self-Supporting Women: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. and legal material regarding a Property Agreement with IA, Inc., 1937–1951 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Clarion Music Foundation: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, 1954–1966 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Cohen, Joseph J.: Donations, Closed Files. Includes photographs, 1954–1966 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Florence Crittenton League: Donations, Closed Files, 1953–1965 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Duke Hospital – Social Service Department: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1940–1952 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Duke University: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1949–1959 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Duke University School of Medicine – Dean W.C. Davison (Board Member): Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1948-1954 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Educational Broadcasting – Channel 13: Donations, Closed Files, 1962–1968 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Encampment for Citizenship: Donations, Closed Files, 1957–1962 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Episcopal Church Foundation – Indian Missions: Donations, Closed Files, 1952–1959 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Fellowship of Southern Churchmen: Donations, Closed Files, 1952–1956 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Festival Foundation: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, 1957–1967 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Field Foundation: Donations, Closed Files, 1951–1957 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Franco-American Audio-Visual Distribution Center: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, 1950–1951 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Friends of the Land (Louis Bromfield Memorial): Donations, Closed Files. Includes clipping, 1940, 1957–1958, 1964–1965 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Furst, Georgea T. (Former Independent Aid, employee): Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Doris Duke regarding travels abroad with Margaret Sanger, 1952–1963 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - George Junior Republic: Donations, Closed Files, 1958–1966 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Girl Scouts of the United States of America: Donations, Closed Files. Includes photographs and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1962 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Girls’ Branch Public Schools Athletic League of the City of New York: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1951–1968 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Girls’ Service League: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1952–1967 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Goddard Neighborhood Center: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1948–1955 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Handicapped Children’s Home Service: Donations, Closed Files, 1955–1963 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Haskin, Helen: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1944–1961 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Hazard, The Misses: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1943–1953 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Henry Street Settlement: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, photograph, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1935–1973 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Hervey, Harry: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1951 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Highland Hospital (North Carolina): Donations, Closed Files, 1952–1956 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Hiroshima Peace Center Association (Ravensbrueck Lapins Project): Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, 1954–1962 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Homes for the Aged: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1948–1950 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Hospitalized Veterans Writing Project: Donations, Closed Files, 1951–1960 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Hudson Guild: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and 1944 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1957–1972 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Hufty, Elinor (Mantron Project): Donations, Closed Files, 1955–1957 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Hughes, Mary E.: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, 1938–1956, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Hughes, Patricia: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clipping, Certificate of Incorporation of Patricia Hughes, Inc. and debt Notes, 1935–1944 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Human Betterment Association of America: Donations, Closed Files, 1957–1962 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Hungarian Relief Program in Austria – American Friends Service Committee, National Catholic Welfare Council, and Church World Service: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, 1956–1957 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Hunter College – Adult Hearing and Rehabilitation Project: Donations, Closed Files, 1955–1961 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Hunterdon Medical Center – Flemington, N.J.: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. and 1955 tax exemption, 1949–1955 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. and 1940 State of Illinois Corporation Certificate,1951 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Industrial Home for the Blind: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. and 1948 Welfare Council of New York City Report on the organization, 1951–1962 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Inglis (O’Neil), Agnes King: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, photographs, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1937–1963 (1 of 2) (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Inglis (O’Neil), Agnes King: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, photographs, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1937–1963 (2 of 2) (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Institute of International Education: Donations, Closed Files. Includes photographs, correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., and correspondence with the State Department and Senator J.W. Fulbright regarding the Fulbright Act, 1946–1962 1972–1973 (1 of 3) (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Institute of International Education: Donations, Closed Files. Includes photographs, correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., and correspondence with the State Department and Senator J.W. Fulbright regarding the Fulbright Act, 1946–1962 1972–1973 (2 of 3) (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Institute of International Education: Donations, Closed Files. Includes photographs, correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., and correspondence with the State Department and Senator J.W. Fulbright regarding the Fulbright Act, 1946–1962 1972–1973 (3 of 3) (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Inter-Agency Guidance Center: Donations, Closed Files, 1955–1961 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - International Information & Program Exchange (H.R.L. Cohrssen): Donations, Closed Files. Includes 1954 tax exemption, 1952–1955 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - International Society for Rehabilitation of the Disabled: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1951–1966 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Jackson, C.D. (former DDF Board member): Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Julliard School: Donations, Closed Files, 1954–1955 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - King Coit Association: Donations, Closed Files. Includes 1937 tax exemption, 1955–1958 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Kirksville College of Osteopathy and Surgery – Dr. Morelock. Includes clipping and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1948–1963 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Klopp, Mrs. G. (Voice Scholarships): Donations, Closed Files, 1962–1968 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Knickerbocker Hospital: Donations, Closed Files, 1954–1956, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - “L” Club for Women: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, photographs, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1942–1950 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Lang, Pearl: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, 1953–1963 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - League School for Seriously Disturbed Children: Donations, Closed Files. Includes 1954 IRS tax exemption, 1957–1962 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - L.E.N.A. – Lower Eastside Neighborhoods Association: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and 1954 IRS tax exemption, 1956–1961 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Lincoln Hospital (North Carolina): Donations, Closed Files. Includes photograph and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1958 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Lovejoy, Albert and Bahija: Donations, Closed Files. Includes photographs and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1949–1955 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Maazel, Lorin: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, photographs, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1940–1946, 1952 (1 of 2) (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Maazel, Lorin: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, photographs, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1940–1946, 1952 (2 of 2) (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Mary L. Merriweather Home for Children: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, 1939 tax exemption, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1949–1957 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology – Displaced Persons Committee: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1951–1952 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology – Foreign Student Summer Project: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1953 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Mind Science Foundation: Donations, Closed Files, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Morningside Community Center: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1959 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Musicians Aid Society: Donations, Closed Files. Includes 1946 and 1961 tax exemptions, 1960–1962 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Narcotics Project – Diocese of Chicago: Donations, Closed Files. Includes map of Chicago illustrating drug addiction, checks, and 1943 tax exemption, 1958–1959 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - National and New York State Associations for Mental Health: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1946–1952, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - National Child Labor Committee: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1949–1958, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - National Committee for Careers in Medical Technology: Donations, Closed Files. Includes 1954 and 1957 tax exemptions, 1957–1961 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - National Committee for the Resettlement of Foreign Physicians: Donations, Closed Files. Includes 1954 tax exemption, 1955–1961 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - National Congress of American Indians: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clipping and 1960 tax exemption, 1962–1965 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - National Council on Agricultural Life and Labor: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, 1952–1956 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Nations Council on Community Foundations (formerly American Foundation Information Service): Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1959 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - National Education Committee – French Teacher Exchange: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1948–1954 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - National Medical Fellowships: Donations, Closed Files. Includes 1947 and 1952 tax exemptions, 1952–1962 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - National Planning Association – Committee of the South: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1949–1954 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - National Publicity Council: Donations, Closed Files, 1952–1954 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - National Scholarship Service Fund for Negro Students: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clipping and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1948–1962 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - National Taiwan University: Donations, Closed Files, 1954–1959 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Neel, Alice: Donations, Closed Files. Includes photograph and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1940–1951 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - New School: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1952–1959 (1 of 2) (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - New School: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1952–1959 (2 of 2) (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - New School – Refugee Fund: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1940–1946 (1 of 2) (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - New School – Refugee Fund: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1940–1946 (2 of 2) (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - New York Blood Center: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and 1961 IRS tax exemption, 1963–1968 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - New York City Ballet – City Center of Music and Drama: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and 1947 tax exemptions, 1952–1960 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - New York Infirmary Building Fund: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1949–1958 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - New York Pro Musica Antiqua: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and 1954 tax exemption, 1955–1965 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - New York School of Social Work – Columbia University: Donations, Closed Files, 1953–1963 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - New York Shakespeare Festival: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and 1956 tax exemption, 1956–1963 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - New York University: Donations, Closed Files, 1952–1956, 1962, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - New York University – Bellevue Medical Center: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1946–1965 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - New York University – Institute of Fine Arts: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1947, 1953–1963 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - New York University – Institute of Fine Arts, Dr. Walter S. Cook: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1939–1949 (1 of 2) (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - New York University – Institute of Fine Arts, Dr. Walter S. Cook: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1939–1949 (2 of 2) (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Newlin, Dika: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1939–1951 (1 of 2) (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Newlin, Dika: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1939–1951 (2 of 2) (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Niagara Frontier Committee to Aid the Sioux (A.R.R.O.W.): Donations, Closed Files, 1955-1956 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - North Carolina College at Durham (formerly N.C. College for Negroes): Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1937–1948, 1952 (1 of 2) (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - North Carolina College at Durham (formerly N.C. College for Negroes): Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1937–1948, 1952 (2 of 2) (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - North Carolina Conference for Social Services: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clipping and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1948–1963 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - North Carolina State Board of Public Welfare – Homemaker Service Project: Donations, Closed Files, 1957–1962 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Northside Center for Child Development: Donations, Closed Files. Includes 1948 tax exemption and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1947–1962 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - O’Grady, Mrs. Anna – Catholic Charities of the Archdiocese of New York: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1942, 1944, 1950–1956 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Opportunities for the Blind: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1947–1951 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Orchestra Da Camera: Donations, Closed Files. Includes 1956 IRS tax exemption, 1957–1958 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Pantheon Press: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1944–1954 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Paraplegia News: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, 1955–1958 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Parsons School of Design: Donations, Closed Files, 1953–1955 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Paschal, Marian, Fund: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1946–1950 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Patchen, Kenneth & Miriam: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1943–1944 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Pemberton House: Donations, Closed Files. Includes photographs and 1948 tax exemption, 1952–1957 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Penland School of Handicrafts – Penland, N.C., Miss Lucy Morgan: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1947–1956 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Pension Plan Activities: Donations, Closed Files. Includes Independent Aid, Inc. material, 1951–1954 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Pestalozzi Foundation: Donations, Closed Files, 1952–1960 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Pickett, Clarence E. (Board Member, resigned): Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1937–1965 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Pitney Hardin & Skinner: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1934–1954 (1 of 2) (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Pitney Hardin & Skinner: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1934–1954 (2 of 2) (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Planned Parenthood: Donations, Closed Files, 1953–1962 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Planned Parenthood, International: Donations, Closed Files, 1952–1959 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Polcer, John and Michael: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, 1963–1967 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Posnakoff, John: Donations, Closed Files, 1954–1958 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Queens Hospital, Honolulu – Dr. Nils P. Larsen: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1937–1941 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Receipts – Desk Company: Donations, Closed Files, 1934–1947 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Reno, Nevada: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1944–1952 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Religious Teachers Filippini – St. Ann’s Convent, Raritan, N.J.: Donations, Closed Files, 1955–1963 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Riverdale Children’s Association: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1944–1949 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Riverdale Children’s Association: Donations, Closed Files, 1951–1960 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Rossi, Lorraine: Donations, Closed Files, 1956–1960 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Sager, Peter: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1951, 1953 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Saint Joseph College – Mary Kable: Donations, Closed Files, 1957–1960 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Salmon Research Foundation: Donations, Closed Files. Includes 1951 tax exemption, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Sanchez, Neftali – George Pepperdine College: Donations, Closed Files, 1959–1960 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Margaret Sanger Research Bureau: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1949–1953 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Schiff, John M. – Board Member: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, 1957–1964 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - School Art League of New York City: Donations, Closed Files. Includes 1950 N.Y.C. tax exemption and 1958 IRS tax exemption, 1954–1968 (1 of 2) (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - School Art League of New York City: Donations, Closed Files. Includes 1950 N.Y.C. tax exemption and 1958 IRS tax exemption, 1954–1968 (2 of 2) (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Albert Schweitzer Hospital Fund: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and photographs, 1954–1961, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Seventh Masonic District Association – Dr. Ginsburg: Donations, Closed Files, 1951–1958 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Shaffer, Audrey: Donations, Closed Files, 1954–1958 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - James E. Shepard Memorial Foundation: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clipping and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1949–1961 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Society of Brothers: Donations, Closed Files, 1952–1958 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Southern Police Institute – University of Louisville: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, photographs, and 1950 tax exemption, 1952–1971 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Southern Regional Council: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1959 (1 of 3) (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Southern Regional Council: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1959 (2 of 3) (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Southern Regional Council: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1959 (3 of 3) (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Spanish American Rescue Mission: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clipping, 1955–1956, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Spence-Chapin Adoption Service: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, 1957–1963, 1966, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - State Charities Aid Association – Child Adoption Service: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1947–1957, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - State Charities Aid Association – Mental Health: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clipping, 1954–1959 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Steckel, Edith: Donations, Closed Files. Includes photographs and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1937–1966 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Synanon Foundation: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and 1960 IRS tax exemption, 1963–1967 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Temple University Medical Center – Institute for Direct Analysis: Donations, Closed Files. Includes 1926 tax exemption, 1958–1959 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Theis, Sophia van Senden (Board Member, Executive Secretary & Treasurer): Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings, 1949, 1953–1957 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Tulchin Project (Simon H.) – State Charities Aid Association: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1945–1948 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - United Negro College Fund: Donations, Closed Files, 1952–1963 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - United States Committee for UNICEF: Donations, Closed Files, 1954–1960 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - United States Committee for United Nations Day: Donations, Closed Files. Includes 1949 tax exemption, 1954–1955 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - United States Olympic Committee: Donations, Closed Files. Includes 1948 tax exemption, 1952–1954, 1960–1966 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - University of North Carolina: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clipping and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1945–1951 (1 of 2) (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - University of North Carolina: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clipping and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1945–1951 (2 of 2) (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - University of North Carolina – Institute for Research in Social Science: Donations, Closed Files, 1952–1958, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - University of North Carolina – Workshops: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1962 (1 of 2) (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - University of North Carolina – Workshops: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1962 (2 of 2) (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Visiting Homemaker Association of New Jersey: Donations, Closed Files. Includes 1963 tax exemption, 1963–1964 (Box 58, Folder 6)